Well, gotta run.
(Alicia:)The guys promised to set up
my satellite dish and paint my bedroom.
(Alicia:)Yay.
(Penny:)Hey. Hey, can I talk to you about that
for a second?
(Alicia:)About what?
(Penny:)Well, you know,
it's just that Leonard and Howard and Raj...
(Penny:)...they aren't like other guys.
(Penny:)They're special.
(Alicia:)Okay, they're special, and...?
Let's see. How can I explain this?
(Penny:)- They don't know how to use their shields.
- Shields?
(Penny:)Yeah, you know, like in Star Trek when
you're in battle and you raise the shields?
(Penny:)Where the hell did that come from?
(Penny:)Anyways,
you know how guys like this are.
(Penny:)So please don't take advantage of them.
(Alicia:)Who says I'm taking advantage of them?
(Penny:)Come on, they're doing everything for you
because you're leading them on.
(Alicia:)So I let them do stuff for me.